# JAZIEL ENRIQUEZ (JAZZ)

Contact info:

Email: jazielenriquez@gmail.com

Github: <a href="https://github.com/yourfellajazz">https://github.com/yourfellajazz</a>

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jazielenriquez/

Phone: 915-888-5233

## PROFILE SUMMARY

Committed to apply my skills in Javascript, React, and psychology. Experience learning and applying skills in front end development via open source and personal projects. Experience in maintaining high standards, caring for others, and thriving in a fast-paced environment. Attentive to detail and excellent at problem-solving. Volunteer experience in serving young adults with their social, developmental, and organizational skills. Effective in utilizing interpersonal skills and connecting with others in the workplace to communicate effectively and better perform assigned duties and tasks.

Sales experience | CPR certified | Bilingual | React.js | JavaScript | Node.js | Bootstrap | jQuery | Redux | JSON/AJAX | GIT | HTML | CSS | ASP.NET|

#### RESUME PROJECTS

### Verse generator

Built with font awesome icons, custom google fonts, custom background patterns, styled components, and Javascript. Mobile responsive. Code is easily modifiable to add asynchronous code with API if needed.

Link: https://yourfellajazz.github.io/verse-generator/

## **Light-Dark Mode**

Built with custom fonts, custom background, styled buttons, Redux and Javascript. Used event listeners, DOM manipulation, and dynamic functions. Code can be simplified to one function instead of two for a cleaner look. (Shown in Github JavaScript file)

Link: https://yourfellajazz.github.io/light-darkmode/

## **Animated Template**

Single page HTML website with inline JavaScript and CSS. Built and modified website with Creative Tim. Cleaned and reduced original code for easier modification. Integrated font awesome icons and custom images.

Link: <a href="https://yourfellajazz.github.io/history-of-the-web-/">https://yourfellajazz.github.io/history-of-the-web-/</a>

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HOSPITALITY TEAM MEMBER - CHICK-FIL-A - 2021-2022

## Responsibilities:

Provided and maintained high-standard customer service in a fast-paced environment by mastering tasks for handling currency transactions, order taking, stocking, and inventory control.

Communicated clearly with customers and co-workers and maintained a positive, friendly, and welcoming attitude.

Resolved complaints quickly, professionally, and kindly.

Adapted to different roles in my position quickly and effectively.

Developed good relationships with customers that made them come back and recognize my service to them.

EDUCATOR - LULULEMON - 2022-2023

## Responsibilities:

Communicated and developed relationships effectively with all my co-workers to create a smooth and better workplace for the company and for my role.

Took initiative to greet and know the customers in order to better suit their needs of coming into the store. Introduced myself and gave information about the product they were interested in while also providing other options if needed.

Adapted to any role that was asked of me to do and asked questions if needed in order to perform my task better.

Assisted customers by asking open-ended questions rather than plain questions..

Maintained a positive, encouraging, and friendly attitude by introducing myself not only to guests but to new co-workers.

Contributed to revenue increase each month by increasing item per transaction sales and offering exchanges to customers instead of returns.

Initiated the possibility of new customers through referrals.

Worked independently and used problem solving skills when it came to customer questions and concerns.

#### **EDUCATION**

UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS AT EL PASO – BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN PSYCHOLOGY, 2022

#### **COMMUNITY SERVICE**

## Youth ministry

## Abundant Living Faith Center, El Paso, TX 2015-2017

Responsibilities: Motivated, lead, and organized a group of 60 kids every Sunday and Wednesday in order to develop and help their personal growth, skills, and maturity.

#### Young adult ministry

#### Abundant Living Faith Center, El Paso, TX 2021-2022

Responsibilities: Communicated and worked together effectively in a group. Organized, lead, managed, and applied interpersonal communication skills in order to encourage and uplift college students to grow in their self-esteem, mental health, and emotional state.

## Food giveaway

#### Abundant Living Faith Center, El Paso, TX 2020

Responsibilities: Teamed up with other people in order to serve the community and help those in need during the COVID-19 pandemic. Loaded food and drinks into vehicles and distributed to those in need.

## **Hospitality Member**

#### Shoreline City, Dallas, TX 2023

Responsibilities: Encouraged and greeted new people. Initiated and introduced myself to new people in order to connect with them and build genuine relationships. Worked together with others to make new people feel welcomed and known.